[{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664145691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":17646,"timeElapsed":159405},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664155356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9664,"timeElapsed":169070},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664164947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9588,"timeElapsed":178661},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":28704,"timeElapsed":207366},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664220180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":26526,"timeElapsed":233894},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664240961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":20778,"timeElapsed":254674},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664252066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":11104,"timeElapsed":265780},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664271118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":19050,"timeElapsed":284832},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664283305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12185,"timeElapsed":297018},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664307792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":21014,"timeElapsed":321506},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664312202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4408,"timeElapsed":325916},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664316722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4519,"timeElapsed":330436},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664334156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":17432,"timeElapsed":347870},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4221,"timeElapsed":352092},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":7518,"timeElapsed":359611},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":8008,"timeElapsed":367620},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664373050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":19143,"timeElapsed":386764},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664377550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4499,"timeElapsed":391264},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664391596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":12386,"timeElapsed":405310},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664395890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4293,"timeElapsed":409604},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664400386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4495,"timeElapsed":414100},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664423108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":22721,"timeElapsed":436822},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664430306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7197,"timeElapsed":444020},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664435116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4808,"timeElapsed":448830},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664439552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4434,"timeElapsed":453266},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664446670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7117,"timeElapsed":460384},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664452720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6049,"timeElapsed":466434},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664468854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":14272,"timeElapsed":482568},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664472032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3177,"timeElapsed":485746},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664477218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5184,"timeElapsed":490932},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664490594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":13375,"timeElapsed":504308},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664506610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":16014,"timeElapsed":520324},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664515074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8463,"timeElapsed":528788},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664520166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5091,"timeElapsed":533880},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664530502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":10334,"timeElapsed":544216},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664534394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3890,"timeElapsed":548108},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664632374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":96188,"timeElapsed":646088},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664635588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3213,"timeElapsed":649302},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664638930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3340,"timeElapsed":652644},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664645406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6475,"timeElapsed":659120},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664648416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3009,"timeElapsed":662130},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664655202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6784,"timeElapsed":668916},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664662528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7325,"timeElapsed":676242},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664665248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":678962},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664668378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3129,"timeElapsed":682092},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664682588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":12681,"timeElapsed":696302},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664685184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2595,"timeElapsed":698898},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664688150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2965,"timeElapsed":701864},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664696876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8724,"timeElapsed":710590},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664703662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6785,"timeElapsed":717376},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664711696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8032,"timeElapsed":725410},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664727518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":15821,"timeElapsed":741232},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664731788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4268,"timeElapsed":745502},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664735884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4095,"timeElapsed":749598},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664787502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":50061,"timeElapsed":801216},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664790780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3276,"timeElapsed":804494},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664793895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3114,"timeElapsed":807609},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664805413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11517,"timeElapsed":819127},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664811474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6059,"timeElapsed":825188},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664816293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4819,"timeElapsed":830007},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664833358,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":17063,"timeElapsed":847071},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664839626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6267,"timeElapsed":853340},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664855124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":15496,"timeElapsed":868837},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664858899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3775,"timeElapsed":872613},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664877471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":17249,"timeElapsed":891185},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664880843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3371,"timeElapsed":894557},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664883983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3139,"timeElapsed":897697},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664894429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":10445,"timeElapsed":908143},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664900806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6375,"timeElapsed":914520},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664927375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":26568,"timeElapsed":941089},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664936045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":8669,"timeElapsed":949759},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664946573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":10527,"timeElapsed":960287},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664950971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4396,"timeElapsed":964685},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664964549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":11982,"timeElapsed":978263},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664967725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":981439},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664970021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2294,"timeElapsed":983735},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664977125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":7103,"timeElapsed":990839},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664980357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3231,"timeElapsed":994071},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664983991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3633,"timeElapsed":997705},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664987157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3165,"timeElapsed":1000871},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664991053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3895,"timeElapsed":1004767},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665001689,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10635,"timeElapsed":1015403},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665011305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":9614,"timeElapsed":1025019},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665034241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":21004,"timeElapsed":1047955},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665042173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7931,"timeElapsed":1055887},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665045235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3061,"timeElapsed":1058949},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665052885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7649,"timeElapsed":1066599},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665055547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2661,"timeElapsed":1069261},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665059815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4266,"timeElapsed":1073529},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665062931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3115,"timeElapsed":1076645},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665066541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3609,"timeElapsed":1080255},{"subjectID":"csajyeny1g","prolificID":"6738c218706186b3fe8e8f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214a0ec719b572963aab","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665071545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5003,"timeElapsed":1085259}]